Past Predator, Present Alien, Future Terminator
Future War is a action, science fiction film directed by Anthony Doublin.
A runaway human slave from Earth's future escapes to the present day.
The Runaway, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Cyborg Master, played by Robert Z'Dar.
Sister Ann, played by Travis Brooks Stewart.
Cyborg, played by Kazja.
Capt. Polaris, played by Ray Adash.
Fred Burroughs, played by Andre Scruggs.
Future War is a 1997 American direct-to-video science fiction film about an escaped
human slave fleeing his cyborg masters and seeking refuge on Earth.
It was lampooned in a 1999 episode of Mystery Science Theater 3000.
The film explores themes of nun, cyborg, bible, dinosaur.
The tone is thought_provoking.